<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The 3DO Interactive Multiplayer, often called the 3DO, is a home video game console developed by The 3DO Company. Conceived by entrepreneur and Electronic Arts founder Trip Hawkins, the 3DO was not a console manufactured by the company itself, but a series of specifications, originally designed by Dave Needle and R. J. Mical of New Technologies Group, that could be licensed by third parties. Panasonic produced the first models in 1993, and further renditions of the hardware were released in 1994 by GoldStar (now LG Electronics) and in 1995 by Sanyo. </text>
		</text>

		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
			<text>3DO Interactive Multiplayer (comúnmente llamada la 3DO) fue una línea de videoconsolas lanzada en 1993 y 1994 por Panasonic, Sanyo y Goldstar (Actualmente LG Electronics). Las consolas fueron fabricadas según las especificaciones creadas por The 3DO Company, siendo originalmente diseñada por Dave Needle y RJ Mical de New Technology Group. El sistema fue concebido por el empresario y fundador de EA Games, Trip Hawkins.

A pesar de su lanzamiento altamente promocionado y su avanzada tecnología, el alto precio de la consola ($699.95 en el lanzamiento) y el sobresaturado mercado de las consolas, condenó la '3DO' al fracaso precipitado. </text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
			<text>3DO Interactive Multiplayer est initialement le nom porté par la première console de jeux vidéo développée par la société Panasonic et répondant au standard 3DO établi par The 3DO Company.</text>
		</text>

			<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
			<text>3DO Interactive Multiplayer foi um videogame doméstico com arquitetura de 32 bits. O 3DO consiste em especificações técnicas criadas pela "3DO Company", que é uma sociedade entre 7 diferentes empresas.</text>
		</text>


				
		
		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Panasonic 3DO</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>