<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The 3DO Interactive Multiplayer, often called the 3DO, is a home video game console developed by The 3DO Company. Conceived by entrepreneur and Electronic Arts founder Trip Hawkins, the 3DO was not a console manufactured by the company itself, but a series of specifications, originally designed by Dave Needle and R. J. Mical of New Technologies Group, that could be licensed by third parties. 
				
Panasonic produced the first models in 1993, and further renditions of the hardware were released in 1994 by GoldStar (now LG Electronics) and in 1995 by Sanyo. </text>
			<text lang="es">3DO Interactive Multiplayer (comúnmente llamada la 3DO) fue una línea de videoconsolas lanzada en 1993 y 1994 por Panasonic, Sanyo y Goldstar (Actualmente LG Electronics). Las consolas fueron fabricadas según las especificaciones creadas por The 3DO Company, siendo originalmente diseñada por Dave Needle y RJ Mical de New Technology Group. El sistema fue concebido por el empresario y fundador de EA Games, Trip Hawkins.

A pesar de su lanzamiento altamente promocionado y su avanzada tecnología, el alto precio de la consola ($699.95 en el lanzamiento) y el sobresaturado mercado de las consolas, condenó la '3DO' al fracaso precipitado. </text>
			<text lang="ca">3DO Interactive Multiplayer (comúment anomenada la 3DO) va ser una línia de videoconsolas llançada el 1993 i 1994 per Panasonic, Sanyo i Goldstar (actualment LG Electronics). Les consolas van ser fabricades segons les especificacions creades per The 3DO Company, sent originalment dissenyada per Dave Needle i RJ Mical de New Technology Group. El sistema va ser concebut per l'empresari i fundador de EA Games, Trip Hawkins.</text>
			<text lang="eu">3DO Interactive Multiplayer (ohiko moduan 3DO dei egiten dena) Panasonic, Sanyo eta Goldstar (gaur egun LG Electronics) enpresen bitartez 1993 eta 1994an abiarazi zen bideo konpainiaren arteko sarreran. Konpailuak The 3DO Companyren diseinuaren arabera fabrikatu ziren, Dave Needle eta RJ Mical New Technology Group-en diseinatuta. Sistema EA Games-en sortzaile eta enpresarioa, Trip Hawkins, izan zen</text>
			<text lang="fr">3DO Interactive Multiplayer est initialement le nom porté par la première console de jeux vidéo développée par la société Panasonic et répondant au standard 3DO établi par The 3DO Company.</text>
			<text lang="pt">3DO Interactive Multiplayer foi um videogame doméstico com arquitetura de 32 bits. O 3DO consiste em especificações técnicas criadas pela "3DO Company", que é uma sociedade entre 7 diferentes empresas.</text>
			<text lang="it">La 3DO Interactive Multiplayer, spesso chiamata 3DO, è una console per videogiochi domestici sviluppata da The 3DO Company. Ideata dall'imprenditore e fondatore di Electronic Arts Trip Hawkins, la 3DO non fu una console prodotta dall'azienda stessa, bensì una serie di specifiche, originariamente progettate da Dave Needle e R. J. Mical del New Technologies Group, che potevano essere concesse in licenza da terzi. Panasonic produsse i primi modelli nel 1993, mentre altre versioni dell'hardware furono rilasciate nel 1994 da GoldStar (ora LG Electronics) e nel 1995 da Sanyo.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der 3DO Interactive Multiplayer, oft einfach als 3DO bezeichnet, ist eine von The 3DO Company entwickelte Plattform für Heimvideospielkonsolen. Konzipiert vom Unternehmer und Gründer von Electronic Arts, Trip Hawkins.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка, выпускавшаяся в 1993—1996 гг. компаниями Panasonic, Sanyo, Creative и Goldstar. Консоль производилась в соответствии с набором спецификаций, предложенных The 3DO Company, и изначально разработанных Дэйвом Нидлом и Робертом Дж. Микалом из New Technology Group. Идея создания консоли принадлежит предпринимателю Трипу Хоукинсу, который также является основателем EA Games.</text>
			<text lang="pl">3DO Interactive Multiplayer (najczęściej po prostu 3DO) – konsola gier wideo produkowana od 1993 przez firmy Panasonic, Sanyo i GoldStar na podstawie specyfikacji stworzonej przez firmę The 3DO Company. Pierwszym celem firmy było stworzenie konsoli gier wideo piątej generacji z napędem CD, które byłyby produkowane przez partnerów firmy na podstawie różnych licencji. The 3DO Company zarabiałoby na opłacie licencyjnej od każdej sprzedanej konsoli i każdej wyprodukowanej gry. Firma oferowała lepsze warunki i niższe opłaty licencyjne (3 dolary od każdej wyprodukowanej gry) dla producentów gier niż konkurencja – Nintendo i Sega. Premiera platformy odbyła się w październiku 1993.</text>		
			<text lang="zh">3DO Interactive Multiplayer，也称为 3DO System 或简称 3DO，是由 3DO 公司开发的家用视频游戏机。3DO 不是公司自己制造的主机，而是一系列规格，松下于 1993 年生产了第一批型号，1994 年 GoldStar（现为 LG 电子）和三洋公司于 1995 年发布了硬件的进一步版本。</text>
			<text lang="ja">3DOカンパニーは、エレクトロニックアーツの共同創設者であるトリップ・ホーキンスによって1991年に設立された、ビデオゲームおよびハードウェアの開発会社です。同社は、1993年に発売された32ビットのビデオゲーム機である3DO Interactive Multiplayerで知られています。コンソールに加えて、3DOは他のプラットフォーム向けのゲームも開発しました。</text>
		</text>
		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Panasonic 3DO</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>FF0000</color>
			<colorEnd>00B63D</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>