<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>Adventure Vision is a cartridge-based video game console released by Entex Industries in either August or October 1982. The monitor, game controls, and computer hardware are all contained within a single portable unit. The LED monitor can only display red pixels. Four games were released, all of which are arcade ports.

Adventure Vision was Entex's second-generation system following the Entex Select-A-Game, released a year earlier in 1981.</text>
			<text lang="es,gl">Adventure Vision es una consola de videojuegos autocontenida (no necesita de un monitor externo) lanzado al mercado por la empresa Entex en 1982, siendo la sucesora de la Entex Select-A-Game. El Adventure Vision era una consola de segunda generación.

Una interesante característica del Adventure Vision era su "monitor", la consola usaba una línea de 40 LEDs rojos combinados con un espejo rotante localizado dentro de la máquina. Esto permitía una resolución de 150 x 40 píxeles.
			</text>
			<text lang="ca">Adventure Vision és una consola de videojocs autocontinguda (no necessita d'un monitor extern) llançada al mercat per l'empresa Entex el 1982, sent la successora de l'Entex Select-A-Game. L'Adventure Vision era una consola de segona generació.</text>
			<text lang="eu">Adventure Vision Entex enpresak 1982an merkatuan atera zuen bideo-joko konsola autoestandarra da (kanpoko monitorik beharrean ez). Entex Select-A-Gameren ondorengoakoa da. Adventure Vision bigarren belauneko konsola bat zen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Adventure Vision est une console de jeux vidéo autonome (ne nécessitant pas de moniteur externe) lancée sur le marché par la société Entex en 1982, succédant à la Entex Select-A-Game. L'Adventure Vision était une console de deuxième génération.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Adventure Vision é um console de jogos de vídeo autocontido (não requer um monitor externo) lançado no mercado pela empresa Entex em 1982, sendo o sucessor do Entex Select-A-Game. O Adventure Vision era um console de segunda geração.</text>
			<text lang="it">Entex Adventure Vision o Adventure Vision in breve è una console portatile per videogiochi di seconda generazione prodotta da Entex nel 1982.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Adventure Vision ist eine eigenständige Videospielkonsole (kein externer Monitor erforderlich), die 1982 vom Unternehmen Entex auf den Markt gebracht wurde und die Entex Select-A-Game ablöste. Das Adventure Vision war eine Konsole der zweiten Generation.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Entex Adventure Vision lub skrótowo Adventure Vision – przenośna konsola gier wideo drugiej generacji wyprodukowana przez firmę Entex w 1982 roku.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Самодостаточная (с собственным экраном) игровая консоль с играми на картриджах, выпущенная компанией Entex Industries в 1982 году. Стала второй игровой системой компании, после Entex select-a-game, выпущенной в 1981 году.</text>
			<text lang="zh">Adventure Vision是由Entex公司于1982年推出的一款自给自足的游戏机（不需要外部显示器），是Entex Select-A-Game的继任者。Adventure Vision是第二代游戏机。</text>
			<text lang="ja">Adventure Visionは、Entex社が1982年に市場に投入した自己完結型のビデオゲームコンソールで、Entex Select-A-Gameの後継機種です。Adventure Visionは第2世代のコンソールでした。</text>

		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Adventure Vision</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>FF0000</color>
			<colorEnd>dddddd</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>