<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>Genre of action and adventure games that are characterized by the displacement of the character through a series of levels in which they must jump, dodge obstacles, fight enemies, and solve puzzles to advance in the story. 
				
They often include enemies and final bosses that must be defeated to advance in the game. This genre has been popular since the early days of the video game industry, with classic titles such as Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman, and Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="es">Género de juegos de acción y aventuras que se caracterizan por el desplazamiento del personaje a través de una serie de niveles en los que debe saltar, esquivar obstáculos, luchar contra enemigos y resolver puzzles para avanzar en la historia. 
				
A menudo incluyen enemigos y jefes finales a los que se debe derrotar para avanzar en el juego. Este género ha sido popular desde los primeros días de la industria de los videojuegos, con títulos clásicos como Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman o Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="ca">Gènere de jocs d'acció i aventures que es caracteritzen pel desplaçament del personatge a través d'una sèrie de nivells en els quals ha de saltar, esquivar obstacles, lluitar contra enemics i resoldre puzles per avançar en la història. 
				
Sovint inclouen enemics i caps finals als quals s'ha de derrotar per avançar en el joc. Aquest gènere ha estat popular des dels primers dies de la indústria dels videojocs, amb títols clàssics com Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman o Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="eu">Ekintza eta abentura joko mota bat da, non pertsonaia zenbaki baten desplazamendua nabaritzen den nola nola maila anitzeko nivelen bidez, salto egiten, oztopoak saihesten, adibidez, borrokatzen ari diren arren, puzlez ebazten hasteko. 
				
Gerta daitezkeen azken jefekin aurre egiteko derrotatu beharreko botereosoak ere barne hartzen dituzte joko horiek. Jokoaren industria hasieratik oso ezaguna da genero hau, Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman edo Castlevania bezalako klassikoekin.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Genre de jeux d'action et d'aventure caractérisé par le déplacement du personnage à travers une série de niveaux dans lesquels il doit sauter, esquiver des obstacles, combattre des ennemis et résoudre des énigmes pour avancer dans l'histoire. 
				
Ils incluent souvent des ennemis et des boss finaux qu'il faut vaincre pour progresser dans le jeu. Ce genre est populaire depuis les premiers jours de l'industrie du jeu vidéo, avec des titres classiques tels que Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman ou Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Gênero de jogos de ação e aventura que se caracterizam pelo deslocamento do personagem através de uma série de níveis nos quais deve pular, desviar de obstáculos, lutar contra inimigos e resolver quebra-cabeças para avançar na história. 
				
Eles frequentemente incluem inimigos e chefes finais que devem ser derrotados para avançar no jogo. Este gênero tem sido popular desde os primeiros dias da indústria de videogames, com títulos clássicos como Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman ou Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="it">Genere di giochi d'azione e avventura che si caratterizzano per lo spostamento del personaggio attraverso una serie di livelli in cui deve saltare, evitare ostacoli, combattere nemici e risolvere puzzle per avanzare nella storia. 
				
Spesso includono nemici e boss finali che devono essere sconfitti per avanzare nel gioco. Questo genere è stato popolare sin dai primi giorni dell'industria dei videogiochi, con titoli classici come Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman o Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="de">Ein Genre von Action- und Abenteuerspielen, bei denen der Charakter durch eine Reihe von Levels bewegt, in denen er springen, Hindernissen ausweichen, gegen Feinde kämpfen und Rätsel lösen muss, um die Handlung voranzutreiben. 
				
Oft beinhalten sie Endgegner, die besiegt werden müssen, um im Spiel voranzukommen. Dieses Genre ist seit den frühesten Tagen der Videospielindustrie beliebt, mit klassischen Titeln wie Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman oder Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Gatunek gier akcji i przygodowych, w których postać porusza się przez szereg poziomów, na których musi skakać, unikać przeszkód, walczyć z wrogami i rozwiązywać zagadki, aby posuwać się do przodu w historii. 
				
Często zawierają wrogów i bossów, których trzeba pokonać, aby kontynuować grę. Ten gatunek był popularny od pierwszych dni przemysłu gier wideo, z klasycznymi tytułami takimi jak Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman czy Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Жанр игр в жанре экшн и приключений, который характеризуется передвижением персонажа через серию уровней, на которых он должен прыгать, избегать препятствий, сражаться с врагами и решать головоломки, чтобы продвинуться по сюжету. Часто включают врагов и конечных боссов, которых нужно победить, чтобы продвинуться в игре. Этот жанр был популярен с самых ранних дней игровой индустрии, с классическими играми, такими как Super Mario Bros, Sonic the Hedgehog, Rayman или Castlevania.</text>
			<text lang="zh">动作冒险游戏类型，其特点是角色在一系列关卡中移动，必须跳跃、避开障碍、与敌人战斗和解决难题以推进故事情节。通常包括需要打败的敌人和最终头目以推进游戏的内容。自从电子游戏行业的早期，这种类型一直很受欢迎，有像超级马里奥兄弟、索尼克·小子、雷曼或恶魔城等经典游戏。</text>
			<text lang="ja">アクションアドベンチャーゲームのジャンルであり、主人公が一連のステージを移動し、障害物をジャンプして避け、敵と戦い、パズルを解決してストーリーを進めることを特徴としています。敵や最終ボスなど、進行に必要な要素が含まれることが多く、スーパーマリオブラザーズ、ソニック・ザ・ヘッジホッグ、レイマン、キャッスルヴァニアなどのクラシックなタイトルがあり、このジャンルはビデオゲーム業界の初期から人気があります。</text>
		</text>

	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>41e7d4</color>
			<colorEnd>00AC97</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>
