<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		
		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Game Boy Advance (GBA) was released in 2001 as the successor to the Game Boy Color. The console featured a color LCD screen and greater processing power that allowed for higher-quality graphics and sound in games. It also included a new wireless connectivity option for playing with other players. 
				
The console had a vast library of games, including titles from popular franchises such as Super Mario, Pokémon, and The Legend of Zelda, and became one of the best-selling handheld consoles of all time. The GBA also had a series of updates, such as the GBA SP and the Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="es,gl">La Game Boy Advance (GBA) fue lanzada en 2001 como la sucesora de la Game Boy Color. La consola presentaba una pantalla LCD a color y una mayor potencia de procesamiento que permitía una mayor calidad gráfica y sonora en los juegos. Además, incluía una nueva opción de conectividad inalámbrica para jugar con otros jugadores. 
				
La consola tuvo una amplia biblioteca de juegos, que incluía títulos de franquicias populares como Super Mario, Pokémon y The Legend of Zelda, y se convirtió en una de las consolas portátiles más vendidas de todos los tiempos. La GBA también tuvo una serie de actualizaciones, como la GBA SP y la Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="ca">La Game Boy Advance (GBA) va ser llançada el 2001 com a successor de la Game Boy Color. La consola presentava una pantalla LCD a color i una major potència de processament que permetia una major qualitat gràfica i sonora en els jocs. A més, incloïa una nova opció de connectivitat sense fil per jugar amb altres jugadors. 
				
La consola va tenir una àmplia biblioteca de jocs, que incloïa títols de franquícies populars com Super Mario, Pokémon i The Legend of Zelda, i es va convertir en una de les consoles portàtils més venudes de tots els temps. La GBA també va tenir una sèrie d'actualitzacions, com la GBA SP i la Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="eu">Game Boy Advance (GBA) 2001ean argitaratu zen Game Boy Colorren ondorengo gainerako bertsio gisa. Konposatuaren pantaila LCD kolorezko bat eta prozesamendu indarrizkoagoa zituen, jokoetan kalitate grafiko eta soinu hobea ahalbidetzeko. Era berean, beste jokalari batzuekin jolasteko bezero-konexio berri bat ere barne zuen. 
				
Konsolek joko-hitz handiko liburutegi bat izan zuen, Super Mario, Pokémon eta The Legend of Zelda bezalako franchise ospetsuen tituluak barne. Guztira, denboran saltzen diren portableen artean, handienetarikoa izan zen. GBAren gainkarga batzuk ere izan ziren, hala nola GBA SP eta Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="fr">La Game Boy Advance (GBA) a été lancée en 2001 comme successeur de la Game Boy Color. La console présentait un écran LCD couleur et une puissance de traitement accrue qui permettait une meilleure qualité graphique et sonore dans les jeux. Elle comprenait également une nouvelle option de connectivité sans fil pour jouer avec d'autres joueurs. 
				
La console disposait d'une vaste bibliothèque de jeux, comprenant des titres de franchises populaires telles que Super Mario, Pokémon et The Legend of Zelda, et est devenue l'une des consoles portables les plus vendues de tous les temps. La GBA a également connu une série de mises à jour, telles que la GBA SP et la Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="pt">O Game Boy Advance (GBA) foi lançado em 2001 como sucessor do Game Boy Color. O console apresentava uma tela LCD colorida e maior capacidade de processamento, o que permitia maior qualidade gráfica e sonora nos jogos. Além disso, incluía uma nova opção de conectividade sem fio para jogar com outros jogadores. 
				
O console teve uma ampla biblioteca de jogos, incluindo títulos de franquias populares como Super Mario, Pokémon e The Legend of Zelda, e se tornou um dos consoles portáteis mais vendidos de todos os tempos. O GBA também teve uma série de atualizações, como o GBA SP e o Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="it">Il Game Boy Advance (GBA) è stato lanciato nel 2001 come successore del Game Boy Color. La console presentava uno schermo LCD a colori e una maggiore potenza di elaborazione che permetteva una maggiore qualità grafica e sonora nei giochi. Inoltre, includeva una nuova opzione di connettività wireless per giocare con altri giocatori. 
				
La console ha avuto una vasta libreria di giochi, che includeva titoli di franchise popolari come Super Mario, Pokémon e The Legend of Zelda, ed è diventata una delle console portatili più vendute di tutti i tempi. Il GBA ha anche avuto una serie di aggiornamenti, come il GBA SP e il Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="de">Der Game Boy Advance (GBA) wurde 2001 als Nachfolger des Game Boy Color veröffentlicht. Die Konsole verfügte über einen farbigen LCD-Bildschirm und eine höhere Verarbeitungsleistung, was eine höhere grafische und akustische Qualität in den Spielen ermöglichte. Darüber hinaus enthielt sie eine neue drahtlose Konnektivitätsoption zum Spielen mit anderen Spielern. 
				
Die Konsole hatte eine umfangreiche Spielebibliothek, die Titel von beliebten Franchises wie Super Mario, Pokémon und The Legend of Zelda enthielt und zu einer der meistverkauften Handheld-Konsolen aller Zeiten wurde. Der GBA hatte auch eine Reihe von Upgrades, wie den GBA SP und den Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="pl">Game Boy Advance (GBA) został wydany w 2001 roku jako następca Game Boy Color. Konsola posiadała kolorowy wyświetlacz LCD oraz większą moc obliczeniową, co pozwalało na większą jakość grafiki i dźwięku w grach. Dodatkowo, zawierała nową opcję łączności bezprzewodowej umożliwiającą grę z innymi graczami. 
				
Konsola posiadała obszerną bibliotekę gier, w której znalazły się tytuły popularnych serii, takie jak Super Mario, Pokémon czy The Legend of Zelda, i stała się jedną z najlepiej sprzedających się przenośnych konsol w historii. GBA miał również serię aktualizacji, takich jak GBA SP i Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="ru">Game Boy Advance (GBA) была выпущена в 2001 году как преемница Game Boy Color. Консоль имела цветной ЖК-экран и большую производительность, что позволяло достигнуть высокого качества графики и звука в играх. Кроме того, она включала новую опцию беспроводной связи для игры с другими игроками. Консоль имела широкую библиотеку игр, включая популярные франшизы, такие как Super Mario, Pokémon и The Legend of Zelda, и стала одной из самых продаваемых портативных консолей всех времен. GBA также имела ряд обновлений, таких как GBA SP и Game Boy Micro.</text>        
			<text lang="zh">Game Boy Advance（GBA）于2001年作为Game Boy Color的继任者发布。这款游戏机拥有彩色液晶屏幕和更强大的处理能力，可以在游戏中实现更高质量的图形和声音。此外，它还包括一种新的无线连接选项，可以与其他玩家一起玩游戏。该游戏机拥有广泛的游戏库，包括像超级马里奥、口袋妖怪和塞尔达传说等热门品牌，成为有史以来最畅销的便携式游戏机之一。GBA还有一系列更新，如GBA SP和Game Boy Micro。</text>        
			<text lang="ja">Game Boy Advance（GBA）は、Game Boy Colorの後継機として2001年に発売されました。このコンソールにはカラー液晶画面と、より強力な処理能力があり、ゲームで高品質のグラフィックとサウンドを実現することができました。さらに、他のプレイヤーと一緒に遊ぶための新しい無線接続オプションも含まれています。このコンソールには、スーパーマリオ、ポケモン、ゼルダの伝説などの人気のあるフランチャイズのタイトルを含む広範なゲームライブラリがあり、史上最も売れた携帯ゲーム機の1つになりました。GBAには、GBA SPやGame Boy Microなどの一連のアップグレードもありました。</text>    
		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Game Boy Advance 2 Players</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>B9B9C8</color>
			<colorEnd>46008C</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>
