<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Game Boy Color was released by Nintendo in 1998 as an upgrade to the original Game Boy. The console featured a color screen and increased processing power that allowed for better sound quality in games. 
				
It was also backward compatible with original Game Boy games, making it a very attractive option. The Game Boy Color had a wide library of games, including titles from popular franchises like Super Mario, Pokémon, and The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="es">La Game Boy Color fue lanzada por Nintendo en 1998 como una actualización de la Game Boy original. La consola presentaba una pantalla en color. También incluía una mayor potencia de procesamiento que permitía una mejor calidad sonora en los juegos. 
				
Además, era compatible con los juegos de la Game Boy originales, lo que la convirtió en una opción muy atractiva. La Game Boy Color tuvo una amplia biblioteca de juegos, que incluía títulos de franquicias populares como Super Mario, Pokémon y The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="ca">La Game Boy Color va ser llançada per Nintendo el 1998 com una actualització de la Game Boy original. La consola presentava una pantalla en color. També incloïa una major potència de processament que permetia una millor qualitat sonora en els jocs. 
				
A més, era compatible amb els jocs de la Game Boy originals, el que la va convertir en una opció molt atractiva. La Game Boy Color va tenir una àmplia biblioteca de jocs, que incloïa títols de franquícies populars com Super Mario, Pokémon i The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="eu">Game Boy Color Nintendo-k 1998an bikoitza, Game Boy originalaren bertsio berritzailea, bultzatu zen. Konsoleak kolorezko pantaila du, prozesamendu boteretsuagoa ere bai, jokoetan audio kalitate hobea eskaintzeko. 
				
Gainera, Game Boy originalen jokoekin ere bateragarria zen, horregatik aukera erakargarri bihurtu zen. Game Boy Colorek joko zabala izan zuen, Super Mario, Pokémon eta The Legend of Zeldaren franquizia ezagunetako tituluak barne.</text>        
			<text lang="fr">La Game Boy Color a été lancée par Nintendo en 1998 en tant que mise à jour de la Game Boy originale. La console présentait un écran en couleur. Elle comprenait également une puissance de traitement accrue qui permettait une meilleure qualité sonore dans les jeux. 
				
De plus, elle était compatible avec les jeux de la Game Boy originale, ce qui en faisait une option très attrayante. La Game Boy Color avait une large bibliothèque de jeux, comprenant des titres de franchises populaires comme Super Mario, Pokémon et The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="pt">A Game Boy Color foi lançada pela Nintendo em 1998 como uma atualização da Game Boy original. O console apresentava uma tela colorida. Também incluía uma maior potência de processamento que permitia uma melhor qualidade sonora nos jogos. 
				
Além disso, era compatível com os jogos do Game Boy original, o que a tornava uma opção muito atraente. A Game Boy Color tinha uma ampla biblioteca de jogos, incluindo títulos de franquias populares como Super Mario, Pokémon e The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="it">La Game Boy Color è stata lanciata da Nintendo nel 1998 come aggiornamento della Game Boy originale. La console presentava uno schermo a colori. Inoltre, includeva una maggiore potenza di elaborazione che consentiva una migliore qualità del suono nei giochi. 
				
Era anche compatibile con i giochi della Game Boy originale, rendendola un'opzione molto attraente. La Game Boy Color aveva una vasta biblioteca di giochi, tra cui titoli di franchise popolari come Super Mario, Pokémon e The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="de">Der Game Boy Color wurde 1998 von Nintendo als Upgrade des Original Game Boy veröffentlicht. Die Konsole hatte einen Farbbildschirm und eine höhere Prozessorleistung, die eine bessere Klangqualität in den Spielen ermöglichte. 
				
Außerdem war sie abwärtskompatibel mit den Spielen des Original Game Boy, was sie zu einer sehr attraktiven Option machte. Der Game Boy Color hatte eine umfangreiche Spielebibliothek, darunter beliebte Franchises wie Super Mario, Pokémon und The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="pl">Game Boy Color został wydany przez Nintendo w 1998 roku jako uaktualnienie oryginalnego Game Boya. Konsola posiadała ekran kolorowy i większą moc przetwarzania, co pozwalało na lepszą jakość dźwięku w grach. 
				
Ponadto, była kompatybilna z grami oryginalnego Game Boya, co czyniło ją bardzo atrakcyjną opcją. Game Boy Color miał szeroką bibliotekę gier, w tym tytuły popularnych serii takich jak Super Mario, Pokémon i The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="ru">Game Boy Color был выпущен компанией Nintendo в 1998 году в качестве обновления оригинальной Game Boy. Консоль имела цветной экран и большую мощность обработки, что позволяло обеспечивать лучшее звуковое качество в играх. Кроме того, она была совместима с играми оригинального Game Boy, что делало ее очень привлекательным вариантом. У Game Boy Color была обширная библиотека игр, включая популярные франшизы, такие как Super Mario, Pokémon и The Legend of Zelda.</text>        
			<text lang="zh">Game Boy Color于1998年由任天堂推出，是Game Boy的升级版本。该游戏机具有彩色屏幕，以及更强的处理能力，可以在游戏中提供更好的音质。此外，它还兼容原版Game Boy的游戏，使其成为一种非常有吸引力的选择。Game Boy Color有一个广泛的游戏库，包括Super Mario、精灵宝可梦和塞尔达传说等热门系列。</text>        
			<text lang="ja">ニンテンドーは1998年にGame Boy ColorをGame Boyのアップグレードとして発売しました。このコンソールはカラーディスプレイを備えていました。また、より強力な処理能力を備え、ゲームの音質を向上させることができました。さらに、Game Boyのゲームと互換性があったため、非常に魅力的なオプションになりました。Game Boy Colorには、Super Mario、ポケモン、The Legend of Zeldaなどの人気のあるフランチャイズのタイトルを含む、広範なゲームライブラリがありました。</text>        
		</text>	

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Game Boy Color (2 Players)</text>
			<text lang="es,ca,eu">Game Boy Color (2 Jugadores)</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>990033</color>
			<colorEnd>669900</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>