<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is an open-source emulator software that allows users to play and enjoy classic arcade games on computers and other devices. It can emulate a wide variety of old arcade systems, including games from the 1970s to the 2000s. The software is capable of emulating the functionality of the original arcade boards with the aim of preserving decades of arcade gaming history that would otherwise be lost or forgotten.</text>        
			<text lang="es">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) es un software emulador de código abierto que permite a los usuarios jugar y disfrutar de juegos de arcade clásicos en ordenadores y otros dispositivos. Puede emular una gran variedad de sistemas de arcade antiguos, incluyendo juegos desde la década de 1970 hasta la de 2000. El software es capaz de emular la funcionalidad de las placas originales con el objetivo de preservar décadas de historia de los videojuegos arcade, que de otra manera se perderían o serían olvidados.</text>        
			<text lang="ca">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) és un programari d'emulador de codi obert que permet als usuaris jugar i gaudir de jocs d'arcade clàssics en ordinadors i altres dispositius. Pot emular una gran varietat de sistemes d'arcade antics, incloent jocs des de la dècada de 1970 fins a la de 2000. El programari és capaç d'emular la funcionalitat de les plaques originals amb l'objectiu de preservar dècades d'història dels videojocs arcade, que d'una altra manera es perdrien o serien oblidats.</text>        
			<text lang="eu">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) software emuladore bertsio irekiko da, eskaintzen dihardutenek ordinateka eta beste gailuetan arcade jokoen gozoa eta jokoa izan dezaten. 1970etako hamarkadatik 2000eko hamarkadara arteko jokalarien multzo zabala emulatu dezake. Programak originalen plataformen funtzionaltasuna emulatu dezake, arcade videojokoetako hamarkadetan garaiak gorde nahi dituen helburuarekin.</text>        
			<text lang="fr">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) est un logiciel émulateur open-source qui permet aux utilisateurs de jouer et de profiter de jeux d'arcade classiques sur des ordinateurs et autres appareils. Il peut émuler une grande variété de systèmes d'arcade anciens, y compris des jeux des années 1970 aux années 2000. Le logiciel est capable d'émuler la fonctionnalité des cartes originales dans le but de préserver des décennies d'histoire du jeu d'arcade qui seraient autrement perdues ou oubliées.</text>        
			<text lang="pt">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) é um software emulador de código aberto que permite aos usuários jogar e desfrutar de jogos de arcade clássicos em computadores e outros dispositivos. Ele pode emular uma grande variedade de sistemas de arcade antigos, incluindo jogos da década de 1970 até a de 2000. O software é capaz de emular a funcionalidade das placas originais com o objetivo de preservar décadas de história dos jogos de arcade, que de outra forma seriam perdidas ou esquecidas.</text>        
			<text lang="it">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) è un software emulatore open source che consente agli utenti di giocare e godersi i classici giochi arcade su computer e altri dispositivi. Può emulare una vasta gamma di vecchi sistemi arcade, inclusi giochi dagli anni '70 agli anni 2000. Il software è in grado di emulare la funzionalità delle schede originali con l'obiettivo di preservare decenni di storia dei videogiochi arcade che altrimenti andrebbero persi o dimenticati.</text>        
			<text lang="de">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) ist eine Open-Source-Emulator-Software, die es Benutzern ermöglicht, klassische Arcade-Spiele auf Computern und anderen Geräten zu spielen und zu genießen. Es kann eine Vielzahl alter Arcade-Systeme emulieren, einschließlich Spiele aus den 1970er bis 2000er Jahren. Die Software ist in der Lage, die Funktionalität der Originalplatinen zu emulieren, um Jahrzehnte der Arcade-Videospielgeschichte zu bewahren, die sonst verloren gehen oder vergessen würden.</text>        
			<text lang="pl">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) to otwarty emulator oprogramowania umożliwiający użytkownikom grę i korzystanie z klasycznych gier arcade na komputerach i innych urządzeniach. Może emulować wiele starych systemów arcade, w tym gry od lat 70. do 2000. Oprogramowanie jest w stanie emulować funkcjonalność oryginalnych płyt w celu zachowania dziesięcioleci historii gier arcade, które w innym przypadku zostałyby utracone lub zapomniane.</text>        
			<text lang="ru">M.A.M.E. (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) - это программное обеспечение эмулятора с открытым исходным кодом, которое позволяет пользователям играть и наслаждаться классическими играми для автоматов на компьютерах и других устройствах. Оно может эмулировать множество старых систем автоматов, включая игры с 1970-х до 2000-х годов. Программное обеспечение способно эмулировать функциональность оригинальных плат с целью сохранения десятилетий истории аркадных видеоигр, которые в противном случае были бы утеряны или забыты.</text>        
			<text lang="zh">M.A.M.E.（Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator）是一个开源模拟器软件，使用户可以在计算机和其他设备上玩和享受经典的街机游戏。它可以模拟广泛的旧街机系统，包括从1970年代到2000年代的游戏。该软件能够模拟原始板的功能，以保护街机游戏历史的数十年，否则这些历史将会丢失或遗忘。</text>        
			<text lang="ja">M.A.M.E.（Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator）は、オープンソースのエミュレーターソフトウェアであり、ユーザーがコンピューターやその他のデバイスでアーケードゲームのクラシックをプレイし楽しむことを可能にします。 1970年代から2000年代までの様々なアーケードシステムをエミュレートできます。 ソフトウェアは、オリジナルの基板の機能をエミュレートすることができ、アーケードビデオゲームの数十年にわたる歴史を保存することを目的としています。それ以外の場合、それらは失われたり忘れられたりする可能性があります。</text>        

		</text>	

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Arcade M.A.M.E.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
