<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text lang="en">The Neo Geo Pocket Color is a handheld video game console released by SNK in 1998. It features a color screen and a cartridge-based system for playing games. The console was designed to compete with the Nintendo Game Boy Color, but it had a smaller library of games due to limited third-party support. Despite its short lifespan, the Neo Geo Pocket Color is still beloved by retro gaming enthusiasts for its solid construction and unique library of games.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Neo Geo Pocket Color es una consola de videojuegos portátil lanzada por SNK en 1998. Cuenta con una pantalla a color y un sistema basado en cartuchos para reproducir juegos. La consola fue diseñada para competir con la Nintendo Game Boy Color, pero tenía una biblioteca más pequeña de juegos debido al limitado soporte de terceros. A pesar de su corta vida útil, la Neo Geo Pocket Color sigue siendo querida por los entusiastas de los juegos retro por su construcción sólida y su biblioteca única de juegos.</text>			
			<text lang="ca">La Neo Geo Pocket Color és una consola de videojocs portàtil llançada per SNK el 1998. Compta amb una pantalla a color i un sistema basat en cartutxos per reproduir jocs. La consola va ser dissenyada per competir amb la Nintendo Game Boy Color, però tenia una biblioteca més petita de jocs degut al limitat suport de tercers. Malgrat la seva curta vida útil, la Neo Geo Pocket Color segueix sent molt apreciada pels aficionats als jocs retro per la seva construcció sòlida i la seva biblioteca única de jocs. </text>
			<text lang="eu">Neo Geo Pocket Color SNKk-ek 1998an jaio zen jokalari- konsola biribila da. Kolore pantaila eta jokoak erreproduzitzeko kartutxoen sistema ditu. Konsola, Nintendo Game Boy Color-rekin borrokatu dadin diseinatu zuten, baina hirugarrenen konponbidea eduki ezikoz, liburutegi txikagoa izan zen. Bere bizitza laburragatik, Neo Geo Pocket Color retro jokoentzat xxipatzen da jauzi bizi dutenentzat, eraikuntza zapia eta joko bereziak dituela dela. </text>
			<text lang="fr">La Neo Geo Pocket Color est une console de jeux vidéo portable lancée par SNK en 1998. Elle dispose d'un écran couleur et d'un système basé sur des cartouches pour reproduire des jeux. La console a été conçue pour concurrencer la Nintendo Game Boy Color, mais elle avait une bibliothèque plus petite de jeux en raison du soutien limité des tiers. Malgré sa courte durée de vie, la Neo Geo Pocket Color reste appréciée par les amateurs de jeux rétro pour sa construction solide et sa bibliothèque de jeux uniques.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Neo Geo Pocket Color é um console de jogos portátil lançado pela SNK em 1998. Possui uma tela colorida e um sistema baseado em cartuchos para reproduzir jogos. O console foi projetado para competir com o Nintendo Game Boy Color, mas tinha uma biblioteca de jogos menor devido ao suporte limitado de terceiros. Apesar de sua curta vida útil, o Neo Geo Pocket Color continua sendo apreciado pelos entusiastas de jogos retrô por sua construção sólida e sua biblioteca única de jogos.</text>
			<text lang="it">La Neo Geo Pocket Color è una console per videogiochi portatile lanciata da SNK nel 1998. Dispone di uno schermo a colori e di un sistema basato su cartucce per riprodurre giochi. La console è stata progettata per competere con il Nintendo Game Boy Color, ma aveva una libreria di giochi più piccola a causa del limitato supporto dei terzi. Nonostante la sua breve durata, la Neo Geo Pocket Color è ancora apprezzata dagli appassionati di giochi retrò per la sua costruzione solida e la sua libreria unica di giochi. </text>
			<text lang="de">Die Neo Geo Pocket Color ist eine tragbare Videospielkonsole, die 1998 von SNK auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Sie verfügt über einen Farbbildschirm und ein System, das auf Modulen basiert, um Spiele zu spielen. Die Konsole wurde entworfen, um mit dem Nintendo Game Boy Color zu konkurrieren, hatte aber aufgrund der begrenzten Unterstützung von Drittanbietern eine kleinere Spielebibliothek. Trotz ihrer kurzen Lebensdauer ist die Neo Geo Pocket Color bei Retro-Spielfans aufgrund ihrer soliden Bauweise und ihrer einzigartigen Bibliothek von Spielen sehr beliebt.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Neo Geo Pocket Color to przenośna konsola do gier, którą wyprodukowała w 1998 roku firma SNK. Posiada kolorowy ekran i system oparty na wkładkach do odtwarzania gier. Konsola została zaprojektowana w celu rywalizacji z Nintendo Game Boy Color, ale miała mniejszą bibliotekę gier z powodu ograniczonego wsparcia ze strony innych producentów. Mimo swojego krótkiego cyklu życia, Neo Geo Pocket Color cieszy się wielką popularnością wśród miłośników gier retro ze względu na swoją solidną konstrukcję i unikalną bibliotekę gier. </text>
			<text lang="ru">Neo Geo Pocket Color - портативная игровая консоль, выпущенная SNK в 1998 году. Она имеет цветной экран и систему на основе картриджей для воспроизведения игр. Консоль была разработана для конкуренции с Nintendo Game Boy Color, но имела более маленькую библиотеку игр из-за ограниченной поддержки третьих лиц. Несмотря на ее короткий срок службы, Neo Geo Pocket Color до сих пор пользуется популярностью среди любителей ретро-игр за ее прочную конструкцию и уникальную библиотеку игр.</text>
			<text lang="zh">Neo Geo Pocket Color是SNK于1998年推出的便携式游戏机。它配备了一个彩色屏幕和基于卡带的系统来播放游戏。这台游戏机旨在与任天堂Game Boy Color竞争，但由于第三方的支持有限，它的游戏库更小。尽管其使用寿命很短，但Neo Geo Pocket Color仍然受到复古游戏爱好者的喜爱，因为其坚固的构造和独特的游戏库。 </text>
			<text lang="ja">Neo Geo Pocket Colorは、SNKが1998年に発売した携帯型ゲーム機です。カラー液晶画面と、ゲームを再生するためにカートリッジに基づくシステムが特徴です。このゲーム機は、任天堂のゲームボーイカラーと競合するために設計されましたが、サードパーティーのサポートが限定されていたため、より小さなゲームライブラリを持っていました。その短い寿命にもかかわらず、Neo Geo Pocket Colorは、堅牢な構造とユニークなゲームライブラリのために、レトロゲームのファンに愛され続けています。</text>
		</text>
		

	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static" ifHelpPrompts="true">
			<color>FF0000</color>
			<colorEnd>99B3FF</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>
