<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The PlayStation is Sony's first video game console. It was released on December 3, 1994 in Japan and is considered the most successful video game console of the fifth generation in terms of both sales and popularity. It ended up establishing the CD-ROM as a support, although other consoles had been doing so for some time. In the late 80s, Nintendo agreed with Sony to develop a peripheral for SNES that would support games on CD-ROM. After many differences between the two companies, they finally did not reach an agreement and Sony decided to develop its own console. 
				
It is estimated that it sold 105 million units in ten years, and its impressive library has more than 3000 titles, including popular and beloved games such as Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider, and Gran Turismo, among many others.</text>
			<text lang="es">PlayStation es la primera videoconsola de Sony. Lanzada el 3 de diciembre de 1994 en Japón, se considera la videoconsola más exitosa de la quinta generación tanto en ventas como en popularidad y acabó implantando el CD-ROM como soporte, aunque otras consolas ya lo hacían desde hace tiempo. A finales de los 80, Nintendo acordó con Sony desarrollar un periférico para SNES que diera soporte a juegos en CD-ROM. Tras muchas diferencias entre ambas compañías, finalmente no llegaron a un acuerdo y Sony decidió desarrollar su propia consola. 
				
Se estima que pudo vender 105 millones de unidades en diez años, y su impresionante biblioteca cuenta con más de 3000 títulos y con juegos tan populares y queridos como Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider o Gran Turismo entre muchísimos otros.</text>
			<text lang="ca">La PlayStation és la primera consola de videojocs de Sony. Va ser llançada el 3 de desembre de 1994 a Japó i és considerada la consola de videojocs més exitosa de la cinquena generació en termes de vendes i popularitat. Va acabar establint el CD-ROM com a suport, encara que altres consoles ja ho havien estat fent durant un temps. A finals dels 80, Nintendo va acordar amb Sony desenvolupar un perifèric per a SNES que donés suport a jocs en CD-ROM. Després de moltes diferències entre les dues empreses, finalment no van arribar a un acord i Sony va decidir desenvolupar la seva pròpia consola. 
				
Es calcula que va vendre 105 milions d'unitats en deu anys i la seva impressionant biblioteca té més de 3000 títols, incloent jocs populars i estimats com Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider i Gran Turismo, entre molts altres.</text>        
			<text lang="eu">PlayStation Sony-ren lehen videojokoen konpiladorea da. 1994ko abenduaren 3an japonian argitaratu zen eta salmenta eta nabaritzearen aldetik, hirugarren sasoiko konpiladore arrakastatsuena da. Baina beste konpiladore batzuk jada egiten ari ziren CD-ROM bezalako sostengaiarekin. Azken hamarkadako amaieran, Nintendo-ek Sony-ri SNES-entzako periferiko bat garatzea ados egin zuen, CD-ROM bidezko jokoak onartu ahal izateko. Bi enpresen arteko askatasunak gertatutako ezberdintasun ugariengatik, azken batean ez ziren akordiora iritsi eta Sony-k bere konpiladore propioa garatu zuela erabaki zuen.
				
10 urtean 105 milioi unitate saldu ziren eta bere liburutegi impresionagarriak 3000 baino gehiagoko izenburuak ditu, Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider eta Gran Turismo bezalako joko ezagun eta maiteak barne.</text>        
			<text lang="fr">La PlayStation est la première console de jeux vidéo de Sony. Elle a été lancée le 3 décembre 1994 au Japon et est considérée comme la console de jeux vidéo la plus réussie de la cinquième génération en termes de ventes et de popularité. Elle a finalement établi le CD-ROM comme support, bien que d'autres consoles l'aient déjà fait depuis un certain temps. À la fin des années 80, Nintendo a accepté de développer avec Sony un périphérique pour la SNES qui prendrait en charge les jeux sur CD-ROM. Après de nombreuses différences entre les deux entreprises, ils n'ont finalement pas conclu d'accord et Sony a décidé de développer sa propre console. 
				
On estime qu'elle a vendu 105 millions d'unités en dix ans et sa bibliothèque impressionnante compte plus de 7 800 titres, dont des jeux populaires et aimés tels que Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider et Gran Turismo, entre autres.</text>        
			<text lang="pt">O PlayStation é o primeiro console de jogos da Sony. Foi lançado em 3 de dezembro de 1994 no Japão e é considerado o console de videogame mais bem-sucedido da quinta geração em termos de vendas e popularidade. Acabou estabelecendo o CD-ROM como suporte, embora outros consoles já o fizessem há algum tempo. No final dos anos 80, a Nintendo concordou com a Sony em desenvolver um periférico para SNES que suportaria jogos em CD-ROM. Depois de muitas diferenças entre as duas empresas, elas finalmente não chegaram a um acordo e a Sony decidiu desenvolver seu próprio console. 
				
Estima-se que tenha vendido 105 milhões de unidades em dez anos, e sua impressionante biblioteca possui mais de 3000 títulos, incluindo jogos populares e queridos como Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider e Gran Turismo, entre muitos outros.</text>        
			<text lang="it">PlayStation è la prima console per videogiochi della Sony. È stata lanciata il 3 dicembre 1994 in Giappone ed è considerata la console per videogiochi di maggior successo della quinta generazione in termini di vendite e popolarità. Ha finito per stabilire il CD-ROM come supporto, anche se altri console lo avevano fatto da tempo. Alla fine degli anni '80, Nintendo accettò con la Sony di sviluppare una periferica per SNES che supportasse i giochi su CD-ROM. Dopo molte differenze tra le due aziende, non arrivarono mai ad un accordo e la Sony decise di sviluppare la propria console. 
				
Si stima che abbia venduto 105 milioni di unità in dieci anni e la sua impressionante libreria conta più di 3000 titoli, tra cui giochi popolari e amati come Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider e Gran Turismo, tra molti altri.</text>        
			<text lang="de">Die PlayStation ist Sonys erste Videospielkonsole. Sie wurde am 3. Dezember 1994 in Japan veröffentlicht und gilt als die erfolgreichste Videospielkonsole der fünften Generation in Bezug auf Verkaufszahlen und Beliebtheit. Es etablierte schließlich den CD-ROM als Unterstützung, obwohl andere Konsolen dies bereits seit einiger Zeit taten. Ende der 80er Jahre stimmte Nintendo mit Sony überein, ein Peripheriegerät für SNES zu entwickeln, das Spiele auf CD-ROM unterstützen würde. Nach vielen Unterschieden zwischen den beiden Unternehmen kam es schließlich nicht zu einer Einigung und Sony beschloss, seine eigene Konsole zu entwickeln. 
				
Es wird geschätzt, dass es in zehn Jahren 105 Millionen Einheiten verkauft hat und seine beeindruckende Bibliothek mehr als 3000 Titel umfasst, darunter beliebte und geliebte Spiele wie Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider und Gran Turismo, unter vielen anderen.</text>        
			<text lang="pl">PlayStation to pierwsza konsola do gier wideo Sony. Została wydana 3 grudnia 1994 roku w Japonii i jest uważana za najbardziej udaną konsolę do gier wideo piątej generacji pod względem sprzedaży i popularności. Ostatecznie udało się ustanowić CD-ROM jako nośnik, chociaż inne konsole robiły to od jakiegoś czasu. Pod koniec lat 80. Nintendo zgodziło się z Sony na rozwój urządzenia peryferyjnego dla SNES, które wspierałoby gry na CD-ROM. Po wielu różnicach między dwoma firmami ostatecznie nie doszły do porozumienia i Sony postanowiło opracować własną konsolę. 
				
Szacuje się, że w ciągu dziesięciu lat sprzedano 105 milionów egzemplarzy, a jej imponująca biblioteka zawiera ponad 3000 tytułów, w tym popularne i uwielbiane gry, takie jak Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider i Gran Turismo, wśród wielu innych.</text>        
			<text lang="ru">PlayStation - это первая игровая приставка Sony. Она была выпущена 3 декабря 1994 года в Японии и считается самой успешной игровой приставкой пятого поколения по продажам и популярности. Она установила стандарт CD-ROM в качестве носителя, хотя другие приставки уже использовали его в течение некоторого времени. В конце 80-х годов Nintendo согласилась с Sony на разработку периферийного устройства для SNES, которое поддерживало бы игры на CD-ROM. После множества разногласий между двумя компаниями они наконец не достигли соглашения, и Sony решила разработать собственную приставку.
				
Оценивается, что за десять лет было продано 105 миллионов единиц, а ее впечатляющая библиотека насчитывает более 3000 названий, включая популярные и любимые игры, такие как Final Fantasy VII, Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider и Gran Turismo, среди многих других.</text>        
			<text lang="zh">PlayStation是索尼的第一款游戏机。它于1994年12月3日在日本发行，被认为是第五代游戏机在销售和受欢迎程度方面最成功的游戏机。它最终确立了CD-ROM作为一种支持方式，尽管其他游戏机早就这样做了。在80年代末，任天堂同意与索尼合作开发SNES的外围设备，以支持CD-ROM游戏。在两家公司之间的许多分歧之后，他们最终没有达成协议，索尼决定开发自己的游戏机。据估计，它在十年内销售了1.05亿台，其令人印象深刻的游戏库拥有超过3000个标题，包括诸如最终幻想VII、合金装备固态、古墓丽影和GT赛车等受欢迎和备受喜爱的游戏。</text>        
			<text lang="ja">プレイステーションは、ソニーの最初のビデオゲーム機です。1994年12月3日に日本で発売され、販売と人気の両面で、第5世代の最も成功したビデオゲーム機と考えられています。これによって、CD-ROMがサポートとして確立されましたが、他のコンソールも以前から同様に行っていた。80年代後半、任天堂はSNES用のCD-ROM対応周辺機器を開発するためにソニーと合意しました。2社の間の多くの違いの後、最終的に合意に達することはできず、ソニーは独自のコンソールを開発することにしました。10年間で1億500万台以上を販売し、その印象的なライブラリには、ファイナルファンタジーVII、メタルギアソリッド、トゥームレイダー、グランツーリスモなど、多くの人気のあるゲームが含まれています。</text>   
			
		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Sony PlayStation</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
