<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Satellaview is a satellite modem peripheral produced by Nintendo for the Super Famicom in 1995. Containing 1 megabyte of ROM space and an additional 512 kB of RAM, Satellaview allowed players to download games, magazines, and other media through satellite broadcasts provided by Japanese company St.GIGA. 
				
Its heavy third-party support included Squaresoft, Taito, Konami, Capcom, and Seta. To use Satellaview, players purchased a special broadcast satellite (BS) tuner directly from St.GIGA or rented one for a six-month fee, and paid monthly subscription fees to both St.GIGA and Nintendo. It attaches to the expansion port on the bottom of the Super Famicom. 
			</text>
			<text lang="es,gl,ca,eu">El Satellaview fue un satmódem producido por Nintendo para la Super Famicom lanzado en 1995 únicamente en Japón. Salió al precio de ¥ 14.000 (unos 99,59 euros o dólares americanos).

Con 1 megabit de espacio de ROM y 512 kB adicionales de RAM, Satellaview permitía a los jugadores descargar juegos, revistas y otras formas de contenido a través de emisiones vía satélite proporcionadas por la compañía japonesa St.GIGA. Para utilizar Satellaview, los jugadores tenían que comprar un sintonizador especial de satélite (BS) directamente de St.GIGA o alquilar uno por una cuota de seis meses, y pagar cuotas mensuales de mantenimiento tanto a St.GIGA como a Nintendo.
			</text>
			<text lang="fr">Satellaview est un périphérique qui a servi de modem satellite pour le système Super Famicom de Nintendo sorti au Japon en 1995.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Satellaview é um periférico que funcionava como um modem via satélite para o sistema Super Famicom da Nintendo que foi lançado em Japão em 1995.</text>
		</text>	

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Super Famicom Satellaview</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>05a3f8</color>
			<colorEnd>dbc416</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>
