<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Mega-CD, known as the Sega CD in North America, is a peripheral for the Sega Mega Drive console released in 1991. It adds CD-ROM playback capability to the Mega Drive, enabling playback of games in CD format as well as music and video. 
				
Although initially met with mixed reviews, the Mega-CD hosted some classic and experimental games, ushering in a new era in video games with higher-quality cinematics and audio.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Mega-CD, conocido como Sega CD en América del Norte, es un periférico para la consola Sega Mega Drive lanzado en 1991. Agrega capacidad de reproducción de CD-ROM a la Mega Drive, lo que permite la reproducción de juegos en formato CD, así como la reproducción de música y video. 
				
Aunque inicialmente recibió críticas mixtas, el Mega-CD albergó algunos juegos clásicos y experimentales, marcando una nueva era en los videojuegos con cinemáticas y audio de mayor calidad.</text>
			<text lang="ca">El Mega-CD, conegut com a Sega CD a Amèrica del Nord, és un perifèric per a la consola Sega Mega Drive llançat el 1991. Afegeix capacitat de reproducció de CD-ROM a la Mega Drive, permetent la reproducció de jocs en format CD, així com la reproducció de música i vídeo. 
				
Tot i rebre inicialment crítiques mixtes, el Mega-CD va albergar alguns jocs clàssics i experimentals, marcant una nova era en els videojocs amb cinemàtiques i àudio de major qualitat.</text>
			<text lang="eu">Mega-CD, Ipar Amerikan Sega CD bezala ezaguna, 1991an Sega Mega Drive konsolarentzako periferikoa argitaratu zen. CD-ROM erreproduzio gaitasuna gehitzen dio Mega Drive-i, CD formatuko jokoak erreproduzitzeko aukera ematen du, baita musika eta bideo erreproduzitzeko ere. 
				
Hasieran erantzunak nahasleak izan zituen, baina Mega-CD-k joko klasiko eta esperimental batzuk hartu zituen, bideo-jokoetan aro berri bat markatzen, bai eta kinebatikak eta audio kalitate handikoak ere.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Mega-CD, connu sous le nom de Sega CD en Amérique du Nord, est un périphérique pour la console Sega Mega Drive sorti en 1991. Il ajoute une capacité de lecture de CD-ROM à la Mega Drive, permettant la lecture de jeux au format CD ainsi que la lecture de musique et de vidéo. 
				
Bien qu'il ait initialement reçu des critiques mitigées, le Mega-CD a accueilli certains jeux classiques et expérimentaux, marquant une nouvelle ère dans les jeux vidéo avec des cinématiques et un audio de meilleure qualité.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Mega-CD, conhecido como Sega CD na América do Norte, é um periférico para o console Sega Mega Drive lançado em 1991. Ele adiciona capacidade de reprodução de CD-ROM ao Mega Drive, permitindo a reprodução de jogos no formato de CD, bem como a reprodução de música e vídeo. 
				
Embora inicialmente tenha recebido críticas mistas, o Mega-CD abrigou alguns jogos clássicos e experimentais, marcando uma nova era nos videogames com cinematics e áudio de maior qualidade.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Mega-CD, noto come Sega CD in Nord America, è un periferico per la console Sega Mega Drive rilasciato nel 1991. Aggiunge capacità di riproduzione di CD-ROM alla Mega Drive, consentendo la riproduzione di giochi in formato CD, nonché la riproduzione di musica e video. 
				
Sebbene inizialmente abbia ricevuto critiche miste, il Mega-CD ha ospitato alcuni giochi classici e sperimentali, segnando una nuova era nei videogiochi con cinematiche e audio di maggiore qualità.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Mega-CD, in Nordamerika als Sega CD bekannt, ist ein Peripheriegerät für die Sega Mega Drive-Konsole, das 1991 veröffentlicht wurde. Es fügt der Mega Drive die Fähigkeit zur CD-ROM-Wiedergabe hinzu, was die Wiedergabe von Spielen im CD-Format sowie von Musik und Video ermöglicht. 
				
Obwohl es anfangs gemischte Kritiken erhielt, beherbergte das Mega-CD einige klassische und experimentelle Spiele und markierte eine neue Ära in Videospielen mit hochwertigen Zwischensequenzen und Audio.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Mega-CD, znane w Ameryce Północnej jako Sega CD, to urządzenie peryferyjne dla konsoli Sega Mega Drive wydane w 1991 roku. Dodaje zdolność odtwarzania płyt CD-ROM do Mega Drive, umożliwiając odtwarzanie gier w formacie CD oraz muzyki i wideo. 
				
Choć początkowo spotkało się z mieszana reakcją, Mega-CD zawierało kilka klasycznych i eksperymentalnych gier, otwierając nową erę w grach wideo z kinematograficznymi i lepszej jakości dźwiękiem.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Mega-CD, известный в Северной Америке как Sega CD, - это периферийное устройство для консоли Sega Mega Drive, выпущенное в 1991 году. Оно добавляет возможность воспроизведения CD-ROM к Mega Drive, позволяя воспроизводить игры в формате CD, а также музыку и видео. Хотя изначально оно получило смешанные отзывы, Mega-CD содержало несколько классических и экспериментальных игр, открывая новую эру в видеоиграх с кинематографическими и более качественными звуками.</text>
			<text lang="zh-CN">Mega-CD，在北美被称为Sega CD，是1991年推出的用于世嘉Mega Drive控制台的外设。它为Mega Drive增加了CD-ROM播放能力，可以播放CD格式的游戏，以及音乐和视频。尽管最初受到了褒贬不一的评价，但Mega-CD容纳了一些经典和实验性的游戏，开启了电子游戏的新时代，提供了更高质量的电影和音频。</text>
			<text lang="ar">ميغا سي دي (Mega-CD)، المعروف باسم سيجا سي دي (Sega CD) في أمريكا الشمالية، هو جهاز ملحق لجهاز سيجا ميغا درايف (Sega Mega Drive) تم إطلاقه في عام 1991. يضيف قدرة تشغيل أقراص CD-ROM إلى ميغا درايف، مما يتيح تشغيل الألعاب بتنسيق CD، بالإضافة إلى تشغيل الموسيقى والفيديو. على الرغم من أنه في البداية تلقى تقييمات مختلطة، إلا أن ميغا سي دي استضاف بعض الألعاب الكلاسيكية والتجريبية، مما أدى إلى بداية عصر جديد في ألعاب الفيديو مع العروض السينمائية والصوت عالي الجودة.</text>
			<text lang="he">ה-Mega-CD, הידוע בשם Sega CD בצפון אמריקה, הוא מתקן עבור קונסולת ה-Sega Mega Drive שיצא לשוק ב-1991. הוא מוסיף יכולת להשמעת תקליטי CD-ROM ל-Mega Drive, מאפשר להפעיל משחקים בפורמט CD, כמו גם לנגן מוזיקה ווידאו. למרות שהתקן קיבל ביקורות מעורבות בהתחלה, ה-Mega-CD אירח כמה משחקים קלאסיים וניסיוניים, סימון עידן חדש במשחקי הווידאו עם צילומים קולנועיים ושמע איכותיים יותר.</text>
			<text lang="ja">Mega-CD、北米ではSega CDとして知られる、1991年に発売されたセガメガドライブ用の周辺機器です。Mega DriveにCD-ROM再生機能を追加し、CD形式のゲームや音楽、ビデオを再生できるようにします。最初は賛否両論の評価を受けましたが、Mega-CDにはいくつかのクラシックな実験的なゲームが収録されており、より高品質な映像や音声でゲームの新時代を切り開きました。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Mega CD</text>
			<text region="us">Sega CD</text>
		</text>	
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>86A0CD</color>
			<colorEnd>FFFFBF</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>
