<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		
		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Mega Drive 32X, also known as SEGA 32X (in America) or Super 32X (in Japan), is a peripheral released by SEGA in 1994, which offered a 32-bit expansion for the 16-bit SEGA Mega Drive console. 
				
It was an attempt to extend the lifespan of the original SEGA Mega Drive console by adding enhanced processing and graphics capabilities. Although it offered some impressive gaming experiences, the 32X did not achieve the expected commercial success and was discontinued shortly after its release.</text>
			<text lang="es,gl">Mega Drive 32X, también llamada SEGA 32X (en América) o Super 32X (en Japón), es un periférico lanzado por SEGA en 1994, que ofrecía una ampliación de 32 bits para la consola de 16 bits SEGA Mega Drive. 
				
Fue un intento de ampliar la vida útil de la consola SEGA Mega Drive original mediante la adición de capacidades de procesamiento y gráficos mejorados. Aunque ofrecía algunas experiencias de juego impresionantes, la 32X no logró el éxito comercial esperado y se discontinuó poco después de su lanzamiento.</text>
			<text lang="ca">La Mega Drive 32X, també coneguda com a SEGA 32X (a Amèrica) o Super 32X (a Japó), és un perifèric llançat per SEGA el 1994, que ofereix una ampliació de 32 bits per a la consola de 16 bits SEGA Mega Drive. 
				
Va ser un intent d'ampliar la vida útil de la consola SEGA Mega Drive original mitjançant l'addició de capacitats de processament i gràfics millorats. Tot i que va oferir algunes experiències de joc impressionants, la 32X no va aconseguir l'èxit comercial esperat i es va discontinuar poc després del seu llançament.</text>
			<text lang="eu">Mega Drive 32X, baita SEGA 32X (Ameriketan) edo Super 32X (Japonian) bezala ezaguna, SEGA-k 1994an argitaratutako periferiko bat da, 16 bit-ko SEGA Mega Drive konsolaren 32 bit-ko hedapena eskaintzen zuena. 
				
SEGA Mega Drive originalaren bizitzaren luzapenerako saiakera bat izan zen, prozesamendu eta grafiko hobekien gehitzearekin. Joko esperientzia ikaragarri batzuk eskaini zituen, baina 32X-ak ez zuen arrakasta komertzialik espero egin eta bertan behera utzi zen bere kaleratzearen ondoren.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Mega Drive 32X, également connue sous le nom de SEGA 32X (en Amérique) ou Super 32X (au Japon), est un périphérique sorti par SEGA en 1994, qui offrait une extension de 32 bits pour la console SEGA Mega Drive 16 bits. 
				
Il s'agissait d'une tentative de prolonger la durée de vie de la console SEGA Mega Drive d'origine en ajoutant des capacités de traitement et de graphisme améliorées. Bien qu'elle offrait quelques expériences de jeu impressionnantes, la 32X n'a pas connu le succès commercial escompté et a été abandonnée peu de temps après sa sortie.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Mega Drive 32X, também conhecido como SEGA 32X (na América) ou Super 32X (no Japão), é um periférico lançado pela SEGA em 1994, que oferecia uma expansão de 32 bits para o console SEGA Mega Drive de 16 bits. 
				
Foi uma tentativa de prolongar a vida útil do console SEGA Mega Drive original, adicionando capacidades de processamento e gráficos aprimorados. Embora oferecesse algumas experiências de jogo impressionantes, o 32X não obteve o sucesso comercial esperado e foi descontinuado logo após o lançamento.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Mega Drive 32X, conosciuto anche come SEGA 32X (in America) o Super 32X (in Giappone), è un periferico lanciato da SEGA nel 1994, che offriva un'espansione a 32 bit per la console SEGA Mega Drive a 16 bit. 
				
È stato un tentativo di estendere la vita utile della console originale SEGA Mega Drive aggiungendo capacità di elaborazione e grafica migliorate. Anche se offriva alcune esperienze di gioco impressionanti, il 32X non ha ottenuto il successo commerciale previsto ed è stato interrotto poco dopo il suo lancio.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Mega Drive 32X, auch bekannt als SEGA 32X (in Amerika) oder Super 32X (in Japan), ist ein von SEGA im Jahr 1994 veröffentlichtes Peripheriegerät, das eine 32-Bit-Erweiterung für die 16-Bit-SEGA Mega Drive-Konsole bot. 
				
Es handelte sich um den Versuch, die Lebensdauer der originalen SEGA Mega Drive-Konsole durch Hinzufügen von verbesserten Verarbeitungs- und Grafikfähigkeiten zu verlängern. Obwohl es einige beeindruckende Spielerlebnisse bot, erreichte der 32X nicht den erwarteten kommerziellen Erfolg und wurde kurz nach seiner Veröffentlichung eingestellt.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Mega Drive 32X, znany również jako SEGA 32X (w Ameryce) lub Super 32X (w Japonii), to urządzenie peryferyjne wydane przez Segę w 1994 roku, które oferowało rozbudowę 32-bitową dla konsoli SEGA Mega Drive 16-bitowej. 
				
Była to próba przedłużenia żywotności oryginalnej konsoli SEGA Mega Drive poprzez dodanie ulepszonych możliwości przetwarzania i grafiki. Chociaż oferowała kilka imponujących doświadczeń w grze, 32X nie osiągnęła oczekiwanego sukcesu komercyjnego i została wycofana z rynku krótko po premierze.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Mega Drive 32X, также известный как SEGA 32X (в Америке) или Super 32X (в Японии), это периферийное устройство, выпущенное компанией SEGA в 1994 году, которое предлагало 32-разрядное расширение для 16-разрядной игровой консоли SEGA Mega Drive. Это была попытка продлить срок службы оригинальной игровой консоли SEGA Mega Drive путем добавления улучшенных возможностей обработки и графики. Хотя он предлагал некоторые впечатляющие игровые возможности, 32X не добилась ожидаемого коммерческ ого успеха и была снята с производства вскоре после выпуска.</text>
			<text lang="zh">Mega Drive 32X，也被称为SEGA 32X（在美国）或Super 32X（在日本），是SEGA于1994年推出的外部设备，为16位的SEGA Mega Drive游戏机提供了32位的扩展。 这是SEGA试图通过增加处理和图形能力来延长原始SEGA Mega Drive游戏机的寿命。 尽管它提供了一些令人印象深刻的游戏体验，但32X并没有取得预期的商业成功，并在发布后不久被停产。</text>
			<text lang="ar">ميجا درايف 32X ، المعروف أيضًا باسم سيجا 32X (في أمريكا) أو سوبر 32X (في اليابان) ، هو جهاز ملحق أطلقته سيجا في عام 1994 ، والذي قدم توسعًا بسعة 32 بت لجهاز سيجا ميجا درايف بسعة 16 بت. كانت محاولة لتمديد عمر جهاز سيجا ميجا درايف الأصلي عن طريق إضافة قدرات معالجة ورسومات محسنة. على الرغم من أنها قدمت بعض التجارب الرائعة في اللعب ، إلا أن 32X لم تحقق النجاح التجاري المتوقع وتم إيقاف إنتاجها بعد وقت قصير من الإصدار.</text>
			<text lang="he">המגה דרייב 32X, ידועה גם בשם SEGA 32X (באמריקה) או Super 32X (ביפן), היא תוספת שיצרה חברת סגה בשנת 1994, הכוללת הרחבה של 32 ביט לקונסולת מגה דרייב של 16 ביט. זו הייתה ניסיון להאריך את חיי השימוש של קונסולת ה- SEGA Mega Drive המקורית על ידי הוספת יכולות עיבוד וגרפיקה משופרות. למרות שהיא הציעה חוויות משחק מרשימות, ה-32X לא הצליחה להשיג את ההצלחה המסחרית הצפויה ונוטלה מהשוק די מיד אחרי השקה.</text>
			<text lang="ja">メガドライブ32X、またはアメリカではセガ32X、日本ではスーパー32Xとしても知られる、1994年にセガが発売した周辺機器で、16ビットのセガメガドライブに32ビットの拡張を提供しました。これは、セガメガドライブ本体の寿命を延ばすために、処理能力とグラフィックス能力を向上させることを目指したものでした。いくつかの素晴らしいゲーム体験を提供しましたが、32Xは期待された商業的成功を収めず、発売後間もなく生産中止となりました。</text>		</text>
		
		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Mega Drive 32X</text>
			<text region="us">SEGA 32X</text>
			<text region="jp">Super 32X</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>FF0000</color>
			<colorEnd>006DD9</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
	
</theme>
