<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Tomb Raider saga is an action-adventure video game series that began in 1996, originally developed by Core Design and published by Eidos Interactive. The story follows the adventures of Lara Croft, a skilled archaeologist and explorer who travels around the world in search of ancient artifacts and lost civilizations. During her journeys, she faces dangerous traps, wild environments, and powerful enemies.

Tomb Raider stands out for combining exploration, platforming, puzzle-solving, and combat. Over the years, the series evolved and included a modern reboot that presents a more realistic and deeper version of Lara Croft’s character. With numerous main titles, spin-offs, and adaptations into other media, it has become one of the most influential and recognized sagas in video game history.</text>
			<text lang="es,gl,ca,eu">La saga Tomb Raider es una serie de videojuegos de acción y aventura que comenzó en 1996, desarrollada originalmente por Core Design y publicada por Eidos Interactive. La historia sigue las aventuras de Lara Croft, una arqueóloga y exploradora experta que recorre el mundo en busca de artefactos antiguos y civilizaciones perdidas. En sus viajes se enfrenta a trampas peligrosas, entornos salvajes y enemigos poderosos.

Tomb Raider destaca por combinar exploración, plataformas, resolución de puzles y combate. Con el paso de los años, la serie evolucionó e incluyó un reinicio moderno que presenta una versión más realista y profunda del personaje de Lara Croft. Con numerosos títulos principales, entregas derivadas y adaptaciones a otros medios, se ha convertido en una de las sagas más influyentes y reconocidas de la historia de los videojuegos.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Tomb Raider</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<colorEnd>FF0000</colorEnd>
			<color>7A4DFF</color>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>