<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Sharp X68000 computer is a series of personal computers released by Sharp Corporation in 1987. These computers were known for their power and advanced graphic capabilities, making them popular platforms for gaming and multimedia applications in Japan.
				
The Sharp X68000 was based on a Motorola 68000 processor, hence its name. Although it did not achieve the same level of international success as other platforms of the time, such as the IBM PC compatible or the Commodore Amiga, it remains highly appreciated for its advanced hardware and rich library of games and applications.</text>
			<text lang="es,gl">El ordenador Sharp X68000 es una serie de ordenadores personales lanzados por Sharp Corporation en 1987. Estos ordenadores eran conocidos por su potencia y sus capacidades gráficas avanzadas, lo que los convirtió en populares plataformas para juegos y aplicaciones multimedia en Japón.
				
El Sharp X68000 estaba basado en un procesador Motorola 68000, de ahí su nombre. Aunque no logró el mismo nivel de éxito internacional que otras plataformas de la época, como el PC IBM compatible o el Commodore Amiga, sigue siendo muy apreciado por su hardware avanzado y su rica biblioteca de juegos y aplicaciones</text>
			<text lang="ca">L'ordinador Sharp X68000 és una sèrie d'ordinadors personals llançats per Sharp Corporation el 1987. Aquests ordinadors eren coneguts per la seva potència i les seves capacitats gràfiques avançades, la qual cosa els va convertir en plataformes populars per a jocs i aplicacions multimèdia al Japó.
				
El Sharp X68000 es basava en un processador Motorola 68000, d'aquí el seu nom. Tot i que no va assolir el mateix nivell d'èxit internacional que altres plataformes de l'època, com el PC IBM compatible o el Commodore Amiga, segueix sent molt apreciat pel seu maquinari avançat i la seva rica biblioteca de jocs i aplicacions.</text>
			<text lang="eu">Sharp X68000 ordenagailua 1987an Sharp Corporationek argitaratu zen pertsonaletako ordenagailuen multzoa da. Ordenagailu hauek indarraren eta aurreratutako grafikoen gaitasunagatik ezagunak ziren, horrek egin zituen Japonian joko eta multimedia aplikazioentzako plataforma popularretan bihurtu.
				
Sharp X68000 Motorola 68000 prozesadorean oinarrituta zegoen, horregatik izena hartu zuen. Nahiz eta ez lortu denbora horretan beste plataforma batzuen mailako nazioarteko arrakastarik, hala nola PC IBM bateragarria edo Commodore Amiga, oso estimatua da bere hardware aurreratuagatik eta joko eta aplikazioen aberastasunagatik.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'ordinateur Sharp X68000 est une série d'ordinateurs personnels lancée par Sharp Corporation en 1987. Ces ordinateurs étaient connus pour leur puissance et leurs capacités graphiques avancées, ce qui en faisait des plateformes populaires pour les jeux et les applications multimédias au Japon.
				
Le Sharp X68000 était basé sur un processeur Motorola 68000, d'où son nom. Bien qu'il n'ait pas atteint le même niveau de succès international que d'autres plates-formes de l'époque, telles que le PC IBM compatible ou le Commodore Amiga, il reste très apprécié pour son matériel avancé et sa riche bibliothèque de jeux et d'applications.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O computador Sharp X68000 é uma série de computadores pessoais lançados pela Sharp Corporation em 1987. Estes computadores eram conhecidos pela sua potência e capacidades gráficas avançadas, tornando-os plataformas populares para jogos e aplicações multimédia no Japão.
				
O Sharp X68000 era baseado em um processador Motorola 68000, daí o seu nome. Embora não tenha alcançado o mesmo nível de sucesso internacional que outras plataformas da época, como o PC IBM compatível ou o Commodore Amiga, ainda é muito apreciado pelo seu hardware avançado e pela sua rica biblioteca de jogos e aplicações.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il computer Sharp X68000 è una serie di personal computer lanciati dalla Sharp Corporation nel 1987. Questi computer erano conosciuti per la loro potenza e le loro capacità grafiche avanzate, rendendoli piattaforme popolari per giochi e applicazioni multimediali in Giappone.
				
Lo Sharp X68000 era basato su un processore Motorola 68000, da cui il suo nome. Anche se non ha raggiunto lo stesso livello di successo internazionale di altre piattaforme dell'epoca, come il PC IBM compatibile o il Commodore Amiga, è ancora molto apprezzato per l'hardware avanzato e la ricca libreria di giochi e applicazioni.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Sharp X68000 Computer ist eine Serie von Personal Computern, die von der Sharp Corporation im Jahr 1987 veröffentlicht wurde. Diese Computer waren bekannt für ihre Leistung und ihre fortschrittlichen Grafikfähigkeiten, was sie zu beliebten Plattformen für Spiele und Multimedia-Anwendungen in Japan machte.
				
Der Sharp X68000 basierte auf einem Motorola 68000 Prozessor, daher sein Name. Obwohl er nicht das gleiche Maß an internationalem Erfolg wie andere Plattformen seiner Zeit, wie zum Beispiel der kompatible IBM PC oder der Commodore Amiga, erreichte, wird er aufgrund seiner fortschrittlichen Hardware und seiner umfangreichen Bibliothek an Spielen und Anwendungen sehr geschätzt.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Komputer Sharp X68000 to seria komputerów osobistych wydanych przez firmę Sharp Corporation w 1987 roku. Komputery te były znane z ich mocy i zaawansowanych możliwości graficznych, co sprawiło, że stały się popularnymi platformami do gier i aplikacji multimedialnych w Japonii.
				
Komputer Sharp X68000 opierał się na procesorze Motorola 68000, stąd jego nazwa. Chociaż nie osiągnął tego samego poziomu międzynarodowego sukcesu co inne platformy z tamtego okresu, takie jak kompatybilny z IBM PC lub Commodore Amiga, wciąż jest bardzo ceniony ze względu na swoje zaawansowane podzespoły i bogatą bibliotekę gier i aplikacji.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Компьютер Sharp X68000 - это серия персональных компьютеров, выпущенных корпорацией Sharp Corporation в 1987 году. Эти компьютеры были известны своей мощностью и продвинутыми графическими возможностями, что сделало их популярными платформами для игр и мультимедийных приложений в Японии.
				
Sharp X68000 был основан на процессоре Motorola 68000, отсюда и его название. Хотя он не достиг того же уровня международного успеха, что и другие платформы того времени, такие как совместимый с IBM PC или Commodore Amiga, его всё равно высоко ценят за его продвинутое оборудование и богатую библиотеку игр и приложений.</text>
			<text lang="he">המחשב Sharp X68000 הוא סדרת מחשבים אישיים ששוחררו על ידי חברת Sharp Corporation ב-1987. מחשבים אלה היו ידועים בעוצמתם וביכולות הגרפיות המתקדמות שלהם, מה שהפך אותם לפלטפורמות פופולריות למשחקים ויישומים מדיה מרובתים ביפן. המחשב Sharp X68000 היה מבוסס על מעבד Motorola 68000, מה שמקור שמו. גם אם לא הצליח להשיג את אותו הרמה של הצלחה בינלאומית כמו פלטפורמות אחרות מאותו זמן, כמו ה-PC IBM התואם או ה-Commodore Amiga, הוא נשאר מאוד מוערך על ידי חומרת החומרה המתקדמת שלו והספרייה העשירה של משחקים ויישומים.</text>
			<text lang="ar">جهاز الكمبيوتر شارب X68000 هو سلسلة من أجهزة الكمبيوتر الشخصية التي أطلقتها شركة شارب كوربوريشن في عام 1987. كانت هذه الحواسيب معروفة بقوتها وقدراتها الرسومية المتقدمة، مما جعلها منصات شعبية للألعاب وتطبيقات الوسائط المتعددة في اليابان. كان جهاز الكمبيوتر شارب X68000 مبنيًا على معالج Motorola 68000، ومن هنا جاء اسمه. على الرغم من عدم تحقيقه نفس مستوى النجاح الدولي الذي حققته منصات أخرى في ذلك الوقت، مثل الحاسوب الشخصي المتوافق مع IBM أو Commodore Amiga، إلا أنه ما زال محبوبًا للغاية بسبب الأجهزة المتقدمة والمكتبة الغنية من الألعاب والتطبيقات التي يقدمها.</text>
			<text lang="zh">Sharp X68000计算机是由日本夏普公司于1987年推出的一系列个人电脑。 这些计算机以其强大和先进的图形功能而闻名，使它们成为日本游戏和多媒体应用的流行平台。 Sharp X68000基于Motorola 68000处理器，因此得名。 尽管与当时的其他平台（例如与IBM兼容的个人电脑或Commodore Amiga）相比，它没有达到相同的国际成功水平，但由于其先进的硬件和丰富的游戏和应用程序库，它仍然备受赞赏。</text>
			<text lang="ja">シャープX68000コンピューターは、1987年にシャープ株式会社によってリリースされた一連のパーソナルコンピューターです。 これらのコンピューターは、そのパワーと高度なグラフィック機能で知られており、日本のゲームやマルチメディアアプリケーションの人気プラットフォームとなっています。 シャープX68000はMotorola 68000プロセッサーをベースにしており、その名前が示すように、その名前が示すように、その名前が示すように、その名前が示すように、その名前が示すように、その名前が示す</text>
		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>Sharp X68000</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>f82905</color>
			<colorEnd>500000</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>