<!-- Theme by pajarorrojo
https://github.com/pajarorrojo/es-theme-PlayStation-X 
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Xbox 360 is the second home video game console released by Microsoft between 2005 and 2006. It is the direct successor to the Xbox, and competed with Sony's PlayStation 3 and Nintendo's Wii as part of the seventh generation video game consoles. It stood out for its extensive game library with memorable titles such as "Halo 3" or "Gears of War".
				
It was also the first to add online service integration "Xbox Live", allowing users to connect and compete with friends and players worldwide. This social aspect greatly contributed to its popularity and longevity in the digital entertainment industry.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Xbox 360 es la segunda videoconsola de sobremesa lanzada por Microsoft entre 2005 y 2006. Es la sucesora directa de la Xbox, y compitió con la PlayStation 3 de Sony y la Wii de Nintendo como parte de las videoconsolas de séptima generación. Destacó por su amplia biblioteca de juegos con títulos tan memorables como "Halo 3" o "Gears of War".
				
Además fue la primera en añadir la integración de servicios en línea "Xbox Live", que permitía a los usuarios conectarse y competir con amigos y jugadores de todo el mundo. Este aspecto social contribuyó enormemente a su popularidad y longevidad en la industria del entretenimiento digital.</text>
			<text lang="ca">La Xbox 360 és la segona videoconsola de sobretaula llançada per Microsoft entre 2005 i 2006. És la successora directa de la Xbox, i va competir amb la PlayStation 3 de Sony i la Wii de Nintendo com a part de les videoconsoles de setena generació. Es va destacar per la seva àmplia biblioteca de jocs amb títols tan memorables com "Halo 3" o "Gears of War".
				
A més, va ser la primera a afegir la integració de serveis en línia "Xbox Live", que permetia als usuaris connectar-se i competir amb amics i jugadors de tot el món. Aquest aspecte social va contribuir enormement a la seva popularitat i longevitat en la indústria de l'entreteniment digital.</text>
			<text lang="eu">Xbox 360 Microsoft-ek 2005 eta 2006 artean argitaratutako bigarren etxeko bideo-konzola da. Xbox-en ondoko hurrengo da, eta Sonyren PlayStation 3 eta Nintendoren Wiiarekin lehiatu zen, zazpi gerazioaren bideo-konzolen parte bezala. "Halo 3" edo "Gears of War" bezalako izenburu gogorrezkoekin izandako joko-liburutegi zabala nabarmendu zen.
				
Gainera, lehenengoak online zerbitzuen integrazioa "Xbox Live" gehitu zuen, erabiltzaileei mundu osoko lagun eta jokalariak konektatu eta lehiatu ahal izateko. Sozial honen alde horrek handiagoa izan zen berberotasun eta iraupenari dagokionez digitalaren munduari.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Xbox 360 est la deuxième console de jeux vidéo de salon lancée par Microsoft entre 2005 et 2006. Elle est le successeur direct de la Xbox et a rivalisé avec la PlayStation 3 de Sony et la Wii de Nintendo dans le cadre des consoles de jeux vidéo de septième génération. Elle s'est distinguée par sa vaste bibliothèque de jeux avec des titres aussi mémorables que "Halo 3" ou "Gears of War".
				
Elle a également été la première à ajouter l'intégration de services en ligne "Xbox Live", permettant aux utilisateurs de se connecter et de concourir avec des amis et des joueurs du monde entier. Cet aspect social a grandement contribué à sa popularité et à sa longévité dans l'industrie du divertissement numérique.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Xbox 360 é o segundo console de videogame lançado pela Microsoft entre 2005 e 2006. É o sucessor direto do Xbox e competiu com o PlayStation 3 da Sony e o Wii da Nintendo como parte dos consoles de videogame da sétima geração. Destacou-se por sua extensa biblioteca de jogos com títulos memoráveis como "Halo 3" ou "Gears of War".
				
Além disso, foi o primeiro a adicionar a integração de serviços online "Xbox Live", permitindo que os usuários se conectassem e competissem com amigos e jogadores de todo o mundo. Esse aspecto social contribuiu muito para sua popularidade e longevidade na indústria do entretenimento digital.</text>
			<text lang="it">La Xbox 360 è la seconda console per videogiochi da casa lanciata da Microsoft tra il 2005 e il 2006. È il diretto successore della Xbox e ha gareggiato con il PlayStation 3 di Sony e il Wii di Nintendo come parte delle console per videogiochi della settima generazione. Si è distinta per la sua vasta libreria di giochi con titoli memorabili come "Halo 3" o "Gears of War".
				
È stata anche la prima a aggiungere l'integrazione dei servizi online "Xbox Live", permettendo agli utenti di connettersi e competere con amici e giocatori di tutto il mondo. Questo aspetto sociale ha contribuito enormemente alla sua popolarità e longevità nell'industria dell'intrattenimento digitale.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Xbox 360 ist die zweite Heim-Videospielkonsole, die von Microsoft zwischen 2005 und 2006 veröffentlicht wurde. Sie ist der direkte Nachfolger der Xbox und konkurrierte mit Sonys PlayStation 3 und Nintendos Wii als Teil der Konsolen der siebten Generation. Sie zeichnete sich durch ihre umfangreiche Spielebibliothek mit unvergesslichen Titeln wie "Halo 3" oder "Gears of War" aus.
				
Sie war auch die erste, die die Integration von Online-Diensten "Xbox Live" hinzufügte, was es Benutzern ermöglichte, sich mit Freunden und Spielern auf der ganzen Welt zu verbinden und zu konkurrieren. Dieser soziale Aspekt trug erheblich zu ihrer Popularität und Langlebigkeit in der digitalen Unterhaltungsbranche bei.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Xbox 360 to druga konsola do gier wideo wydana przez Microsoft w latach 2005-2006. Jest bezpośrednim następcą Xboxa i konkurowała z PlayStation 3 od Sony i Wii od Nintendo jako część konsol wideo siódmej generacji. Wyróżniała się obszerną biblioteką gier z takimi tytułami jak "Halo 3" czy "Gears of War".
				
Ponadto była pierwszą, która dodała integrację usług online "Xbox Live", umożliwiającą użytkownikom połączenie się i rywalizację z przyjaciółmi i graczami z całego świata. Ten aspekt społeczny znacznie przyczynił się do jej popularności i trwałości w branży rozrywki cyfrowej.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Xbox 360 - это вторая игровая приставка для дома, выпущенная Microsoft в период с 2005 по 2006 год. Она является прямым наследником Xbox и конкурировала с PlayStation 3 от Sony и Wii от Nintendo как часть консолей седьмого поколения. Она отличалась обширной библиотекой игр с такими памятными заголовками, как "Halo 3" или "Gears of War".
				
Кроме того, она была первой, которая добавила интеграцию онлайн-сервисов "Xbox Live", позволяющую пользователям подключаться и соревноваться с друзьями и игроками со всего мира. Этот социальный аспект значительно способствовал ее популярности и долговечности в индустрии цифрового развлечения.</text>
			<text lang="he">ה- Xbox 360 הוא הקונסולה למשחקים השנייה לבית שהושקה על ידי מיקרוסופט בין השנים 2005 ו-2006. זהו היורש הישיר של ה- Xbox, והתחרה עם ה- PlayStation 3 של סוני וה- Wii של נינטנדו כחלק מהקונסולות לדור השביעי. ידגיש על ספריית המשחקים הרחבה שלה עם כותרים לזכר כמו "Halo 3" או "Gears of War". נוסף על כך, היא הייתה הראשונה שהוסיפה אינטגרציה של שירותים מקוונים "Xbox Live", שמאפשרת למשתמשים להתחבר ולהתחרות עם חברים ושחקנים מכל רחבי העולם. ההיבט החברתי הזה תרם לצלחתה ולאורך ימיה בתעשיית הבידור הדיגיטלי.</text>
			<text lang="zh">Xbox 360是由微软于2005年至2006年间推出的第二款家用视频游戏机。它是Xbox的直接继任者，并与索尼的PlayStation 3和任天堂的Wii一起作为第七代视频游戏机的一部分。它以其丰富的游戏库而脱颖而出，其中包括《Halo 3》或《战争机器》等令人难忘的游戏。 它还是第一款添加在线服务整合“Xbox Live”的游戏机，使用户可以与世界各地的朋友和玩家连接和竞争。这一社交方面极大地促进了它在数字娱乐行业中的流行度和长寿。</text>
			<text lang="ja">Xbox 360は、2005年から2006年にかけてマイクロソフトによってリリースされた2番目の家庭用ビデオゲームコンソールです。これはXboxの直接の後継機であり、第7世代のビデオゲームコンソールの一部として、ソニーのPlayStation 3や任天堂のWiiと競合しました。 "Halo 3"や "Gears of War"などの記憶に残るタイトルが含まれる広範なゲームライブラリで目立ちました。 また、世界中の友達やプレーヤーと接続して競技することができるオンラインサービス統合「Xbox Live」を最初に追加したのもこれです。この社会的側面は、デジタルエンターテイメント業界での人気と長寿に大きく貢献しました。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="system_name" extra="true">
			<text>XBOX 360</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	<view name="system,detailed, grid">
		<image name="linea-inferior" extra="static">
			<color>B3B2B4</color>
			<colorEnd>79C900</colorEnd>
		</image>
	</view>
</theme>
